{
  "card_id": "hank-green-2026",
  "user_handle": "hankgreen",
  "answer_id": "CZdt6NCOcQ",
  "status": "active",
  "win_probability": 0.2004739219855084,
  "target_win_prob": 0.2004739219855084,
  "purchase_price": 1,
  "purchase_prob": 0.5,
  "created_time": 1768533837173,
  "grid": [
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "New dinosaur named for tiktok thing",
      "prob": 0.4061902044378799,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "0Zu86PIs5d",
      "answer_text": "New dinosaur named for tiktok thing"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Beloved actor cast as Elon in biopic",
      "prob": 0.5941744037705292,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "g5nLU8cUln",
      "answer_text": "Beloved actor cast as Elon in biopic"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "I do 1 (one) Pull-up",
      "prob": 0.8287671232876713,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "dQh0qP9qt9",
      "answer_text": "I do 1 (one) Pull-up"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "OpenAI Makes GPT Phone",
      "prob": 0.12886597938144334,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "L82UEuctOC",
      "answer_text": "OpenAI Makes GPT Phone"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "ad supported medical care",
      "prob": 0.4553315571877679,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "50uuRzPgL0",
      "answer_text": "ad supported medical care"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Waymo Car learns to do donuts",
      "prob": 0.24049045098417723,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "AO6CCgyOdS",
      "answer_text": "Waymo Car learns to do donuts"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Trump Declares Himself an Olympian",
      "prob": 0.3570229022955821,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "zOAL5QL6p9",
      "answer_text": "Trump Declares Himself an Olympian"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "T.Swift Married in Montana",
      "prob": 0.062460735192887855,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "REqP2thstn",
      "answer_text": "T.Swift Married in Montana"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "World's First Trillionaire",
      "prob": 0.6581848508488969,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "yIOc8hS0QO",
      "answer_text": "World's First Trillionaire"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "GTA6 Saves or ruins the economy",
      "prob": 0.43057050592034435,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "pCntdLRq90",
      "answer_text": "GTA6 Saves or ruins the economy"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "\"Don't Die\" guy does funniest possible thing",
      "prob": 0.039999999999999904,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "dNSZyIg2Pn",
      "answer_text": "\"Don't Die\" guy does funniest possible thing"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Dark \"Saved by the Bell\" Reboot",
      "prob": 0.3378378419459126,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "9QZuPnZOdU",
      "answer_text": "Dark \"Saved by the Bell\" Reboot"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Measles Outbreak",
      "prob": 0.8767123260685623,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "SL8Lg9n5nI",
      "answer_text": "Measles Outbreak"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Blue Wave",
      "prob": 0.7068980791822403,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "pEhySSuZzZ",
      "answer_text": "Blue Wave"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "NVDA Down 35% From Peak",
      "prob": 0.39136157517298487,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "60yN2pZ28s",
      "answer_text": "NVDA Down 35% From Peak"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Big Youtuber Quits",
      "prob": 0.6282527881040891,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "ZOzytn695I",
      "answer_text": "Big Youtuber Quits"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "New Smell Invented",
      "prob": 0.6548207471737711,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "qlI2Ptquls",
      "answer_text": "New Smell Invented"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Chevy Bolt is a Huge Success",
      "prob": 0.4098360655737705,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "gApnn5U6E0",
      "answer_text": "Chevy Bolt is a Huge Success"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "World's 1st Trillionaire No longer a Trillionaire",
      "prob": 0.4532265603115986,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "Zyly0Ls9t6",
      "answer_text": "World's 1st Trillionaire No longer a Trillionaire"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "New Particle",
      "prob": 0.398699226899006,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "5tQnZLRAEE",
      "answer_text": "New Particle"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Shadow Biosphere",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "cCzsLnLh6L",
      "answer_text": "Shadow Biosphere"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Famous person marries an AI",
      "prob": 0.3223207154857036,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "NOO09gEu88",
      "answer_text": "Famous person marries an AI"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Apple Vision Amateur",
      "prob": 0.3076923076923077,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "t9hsINu5yt",
      "answer_text": "Apple Vision Amateur"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "RFK jr gets himself fired",
      "prob": 0.3701889433170049,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "2uOuulEEsI",
      "answer_text": "RFK jr gets himself fired"
    },
    {
      "slug": "hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Billionaire Sperm Bank",
      "prob": 0.34,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Alfie/hank-greens-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "uR6Czud2LZ",
      "answer_text": "Billionaire Sperm Bank"
    }
  ],
  "card_type": "featured",
  "external_link": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SCtj1bWVoIg",
  "external_link_label": "Watch Video"
}